<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>philipschmidt</title>
    <link>https://philipschmidt.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on philipschmidt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:43:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://philipschmidt.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:43:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>How to Reach Me The best way to reach me is on Linkedin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:36:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Philip Schmidt and I am from St. Paul, MN. In my free time I like to work on side projects to create tools to support cloud services, game on PC or Xbox, travel, go to local events. I am also learning how to speak Portuguese since I frequently visit Brazil to visit family from time to time. My career path is focused on being a customer facing developer creating tools to support cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCI CLI</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/oci-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 16:43:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/oci-cli/</guid>
      <description>https://github.com/schmidtp0740/oci-dev
Abstract This project was purely meant as a fun project to gain more experiance in Golang as well as using the SDKs for Oracle Cloud Infrastructure(OCI). OCI already has a cli built in python so I decided to rebuild it in golang. This would showcase how easy it is to install the oci without any dependecies. I also planned to add some features some technical solutions engineers might find helpful, for instance getting the ip address of a compute instance in one command instead of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EMR on the Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/hc-bc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 16:58:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/hc-bc/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This is a implemenation of what it might look like to put EMR on a permissioned blockchain. There are 3 participants in the bussiness network: doctor, pharmacist, and insurance auditor. The use case that a given patient&amp;rsquo;s prescription would be tracked throughout its lifestyle. Other types of data tracked are blood pressure and heart rate data. This was a team project involving several front end developers. My role in this was to design the architecture of this solution as well as implement the api gatway to access the blockchain ledger on Oracle Block Cloud Service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Permanent Traveler</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/permanenttraveler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 13:45:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/permanenttraveler/</guid>
      <description>A development for a peer for their senior showcase. Designed and Owned by Zach Smith. I simply developed with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>