<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>philipschmidt</title>
    <link>https://philipschmidt.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on philipschmidt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 03:37:12 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://philipschmidt.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup Jenkins X on Oracle Container Engine</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/posts/howtosetupjenkinsxonoke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 03:37:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/posts/howtosetupjenkinsxonoke/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This setup guide will help to setup jenkins-x on an OKE cluster.
Prereqs  Install the OCI CLI Configure the oci profile config file Install kubectl install jenkins-x  Step 1  deploy vcn and resources in OCI  use the network module for a template of how to configure 2 load balancer subnets and 3 public worker subnet with appropriate security list docs on how to configure your vcn for OKE   Step 2 Deploy new cluster in OCI  Create a new oke cluster with jenkins x installed  the regional container engine for kubernetes rest endpoint to find the ocid of the vcn, compartment, load balancer and worker subnets refer to the oci console   jx create cluster oke \ --name=&amp;#34;c2-jx-cluster&amp;#34; \ --docker-registry=&amp;#34;iad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:43:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>How to Reach Me The best way to reach me is on Linkedin</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:36:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Philip Schmidt. If I had to describe my skillset in one word I would say DevOps. The reason is because I have a background in development and ops. On the dev side, I have built cloud-native applications running on k8s and I love to build tools, either cli or web based. On the ops side, I have a background in networking like TCP/IP, DNS, IPSec VPN as I have helped enterprise customers assisted in configuring their cloud networks and IPSec VPN to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCI CLI</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/oci-cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 16:43:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/oci-cli/</guid>
      <description>https://github.com/schmidtp0740/oci-dev
Abstract This project was purely meant as a fun project to gain more experiance in Golang as well as using the SDKs for Oracle Cloud Infrastructure(OCI). OCI already has a cli built in python so I decided to rebuild it in golang. This would showcase how easy it is to install the oci without any dependecies. I also planned to add some features some technical solutions engineers might find helpful, for instance getting the ip address of a compute instance in one command instead of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EMR on the Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/hc-bc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2017 16:58:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/hc-bc/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This is a implemenation of what it might look like to put EMR on a permissioned blockchain. There are 3 participants in the bussiness network: doctor, pharmacist, and insurance auditor. The use case that a given patient&amp;rsquo;s prescription would be tracked throughout its lifestyle. Other types of data tracked are blood pressure and heart rate data. This was a team project involving several front end developers. My role in this was to design the architecture of this solution as well as implement the api gatway to access the blockchain ledger on Oracle Block Cloud Service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Permanent Traveler</title>
      <link>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/permanenttraveler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 13:45:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://philipschmidt.io/projects/permanenttraveler/</guid>
      <description>A development for a peer for their senior showcase. Designed and Owned by Zach Smith. I simply developed with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>